Guide to the Stanford University, Information Technology Services, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-104
  - Professional Organizations: Seminar for Academic Computing Services 8/1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Professional Organizations: DECUS 2/14/1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Professional Organizations: EDUCOM 1/23/1980 - 9/16/1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Professional Organizations: EDUCOM/EDUNET 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Professional Organizations: General 1/17/1972 - 3/1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Professional Organizations: GUIDE 2/1/1978 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Professional Organizations: IEEE 2/18/1980 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Professional Organizations: SHARE, Inc. 7/13/1979 - 6/12/1980 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Professional Organizations: EARF 9/11/1974 -8/15/1980 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Professional Organizations: SHARE Pet 3/21/1972 - 8/5/1980 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Professional Organizations: Telecommunications Association 4/9/1981 - 5/14/1981 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Professional Organizations: Professional Working Group 3/14/1975 - 4/14/1975 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Professional Organizations: EDUCOM Benchmark Program 5/10/1978 - 12/7/1978 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Professional Organizations: EDUCOM 1977 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Projects: Automated Budget 9/11/1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Accounts Receivable System Development 4/23/1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Projects: CIT General 1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Projects: Graphics 4/11/1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Projects: Leave System 3/28/1979 - 9/17/1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Medical Computing 1/9/1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Projects: TFM 4/16/1980 - 7/10/1981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Projects: MICRO/TIRO/SMILE 11/5/1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Projects: ADPS Status Reports 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Projects: SCIP Progress Reports 7/25/1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Projects: Campus Facility Progress Reports 10/12/1977 - 4/29/1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Projects: ADPS Progress Reports 8/1/1977 - 10/13/1979 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Projects: New Financial Accounting Systems 2/28/1979 - 4/23/1979 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Projects: Office Automation 8/4/1978 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Projects: Text Handling Network 3/29/1979 - 12/30/1980 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Projects: SCIP Campus Quarterly Reports 12/22/1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Projects: Word Processing 2/16/1978 - 10/29/1978 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Projects: Project Management 4/19/1971 - 2/3/1978 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Proposals: Proposal for Purchase of Stanford's IBM 360/67 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Proposals: 1980 Office of Development System 7/8/1980 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Proposals: Ariel 2/7/1978 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Proposals: CIT 3/20/1981 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Proposals: Fundraising 2/25/1980 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Proposals: SRI Joint Development Project 1/22/1981 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Proposals: Dialnet 2/24/1978 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Proposals: General 10/13/1972 - 12/2/1977 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Proposals: IBM Joint Networking Studies 9/1978 - 2/19/1981 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Proposals: IBM Joint Study: PUP Software 3/10/1981 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Proposals: Medical Computing 7/1973 - 7/20/1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Proposals: Microprocessors Development Lab 11/17/1978 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Proposals: Other Departments 1/12/1970 - 9/9/1979 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Proposals: SCIP 7/6/1978 - 7/11/1978 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Proposals: Student Service System 3/1/1979 - 7/17/1979 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Proposals: Student Service System 3/15/1978 - 2/2/1979 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Proposals: Systems Software 11/26/1973 - 11/24/1976 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Proposals: Word Processing 10/8/1977 - 10/6/1978 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Public Relations: General 3/17/1969 - 3/28/1980 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Public Relations: Japanese Companies 1980 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Public Relations: Hitachi 9/7/1976 - 5/29/1978 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Public Relations: Publicity, Photographs (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Publications: CIT 11/30/1980 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Quartet Meetings 8/19/1980 - 12/22/1980 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Rates, Computer: CR Rates 3081 1982-83 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Rates, Computer: Computer Academic Computing, from 1974 1/8/1974 - 12/5/1979 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Rates, Computer: RLIN/BALLOTS Computer 10/6/1975 - 6/27/1979 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Rates, Computer: General 11/31/65 - 10/11/1978 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Rates, Computer: Medical Computing 7/20/1973 - 10/30/1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Rates, Computer: Other Organizations 8/69 - 9/1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Rates, Computer: SCIP 7/10/1973 - 11/9/1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Rates, Computer: Other Stanford Computers 10/7/1972 - 10/8/1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Rates, Computer: SLAC 2/5/1973 - 4/27/1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Rates, Computer: 370/168, from 1978 3/10/1978 - 3/20/1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Rates, Computer: 3033 3/7/1979 - 11/13/1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Rates, Fixed Share Pricing 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Rates, Flexible Pricing: General 10/12/67 - 8/6/1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Rates, Flexible Pricing: Reports 10/21/67 - 7/14/1976 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Rates, Indirect Cost: University 7/31/1970 - 10/29/1980 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Rates, Studies: Computer 7/67 - 7/1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Research Administration 1/2/1970 - 11/8/1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Registrar's Office 2/1/1980 - 9/4/1980 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Research Programs: Mexico 12/22/1982 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Projects: Press 11 Project Schedule 10/27/1980 - 11/6/1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Reports: Brown University Broadband Network 7/5/1981 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Reports: CICS Evaluation 7/15/1981 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Reports: A-21 Reporting Systems 8/17/1981 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Reports: PAS Technical Evaluation Group 3/19/1981 - 8/13/1981 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Reports: CIT to Federal Government 8/31/1980 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Real time Users Group RTUG 9/15/1981 - 11/18/1981 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Rates, Computer: 3081 Node Rates 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Risk Assessment Method for System Development Projects 11/15/1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - RLG: Special Committee Working File 1/13/1981 - 6/17/1981 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - RLG: Executive Committee Working File 12/30/1980 - 7/14/1981 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - RLG: Host Institution Review Working File 1/16/1981 - 5/22/1981 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - RLG: Mainframe Issue 11/1982 - 1/1983 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - RLG: RLIN, Amdahl Corp. 6/14/1982 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - RLG: RLIN-11 4/1981 - 9/1982 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - RLG: Stanford 3/1979 - 2/1981 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - RLG: The University of Arizona 9/17/1979 - 7/16/1980 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - RLG: Edward E. Shaw Correspondence & Memoranda 1980 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - RLG: Presentations, includes 1 audiocassette 6/15/1979 - 7/31/1980 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - RLG: Costing study: CIT/RLG 5/1982 - 6/1982 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - RLG: Stanford Cost Allocation 3/29/1982 - 1/17/1983 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - RLG: Stanford Liason 9/1982 - 4/1983 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - RLG: Host Institution Agreement 8/1982 - 8/1983 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - RLG: RLIN 7/1981 - 6/1982 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - RLG: James Schmidt, Vice President 6/1981 - 9/1981 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - RLG: Miscellaneous Correspondence 1/1981 - 6/1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - RLG: Retrospective Conversion of Bibliographic Records Mellon, etc 11/1980 - 1/1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN Advisory Board 6/1/1977 - 12/6/1977 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN Advisory Board Meetings 1977 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN Advisory Board: Cost Analysis 1/17/1977 - 5/25/1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN Advisory Board Minutes 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN NAC (Network Advisory Committee) 1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: Council on Library Resources, NEH 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: CLASS (California Authority for Systems and Services) 6/1977 - 3/1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: Network Technical Architecture Group NTAG 6/1977 - 12/1977 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co. Study 1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: Budget, Revised 5/4/1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: University of California 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: RLG 1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: University of Chicago - Stanford Discussions 12/1977 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: University of California at Berkeley-Stanford Library Co-op Program1977 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: National Computer Science Conference 6/4/1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Salary Setting Procedures 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Sales of Equipment: IBM 2540 12/17/1970 - 6/23/1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Sales of Equipment: General 12/24/69 - 6/19/1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Sales of Equipment: 370/168 9/1975 - 7/1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Science Dynamics Corporation 6/1980 -11/1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - SCIP: Executive Committee Meetings 2/1975 - 9/1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - SCIP: Business and Finance Weekly Reports 9/1976 - 2/1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - SCIP: Audit Reports 1977-78 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - SCIP: Budget 1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - SCIP: Budget 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 8.1)
  - SCIP: Financial 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - SCIP: Financial 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9.1)
  - SCIP: Financial 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9.2)
  - SCIP: Financial 1973 (Box 23, Folder 9.3)
  - SCIP: General 1978 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - SCIP: Plan and Configuration Chart for Main Campus Equipment Acquisition 5/13/1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - SCIP: General 1/1974 - 10/1978 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - SCIP: Licensing and Royalty 1976-78 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - SCIP: Salaries and Selections 1977-78 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - SCIP: Non-Stanford Users Study 1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - SCIP: Task Force on the Future of Computing at Stanford 1978 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - SCIP: Labor Relations 1977 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - SCIP: Study 4/1977 - 7/1977 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Security: General 2/1970 - 6/1980 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Security: Accounting 2/1975 - 6/1979 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Security: Policy 7/1975 - 8/1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Service Operation: University 3/12/1979 - 8/3/1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Shared Mini-proposal 10/1981 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - SHARE 11/1/1982 - 12/30/1982 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN Advisory Board Meetings 1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN Advisory Board Agenda Sept. 8 1976 (Box 23, Folder 25.1)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN Advisory Board Meetings 1977 (Box 23, Folder 25.2)
  - SLAC 7/24/1981 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - SLAC: Computing 9/14/1978 - 5/18/1979 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Edward E. Shaw Speech to University Fellows 5/7/1981 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Projects: Sponsored Projects 7/10/1976 - 5/1982 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Standards: SCIP 2/7/1974 - 11/28/1977 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Standards: Standards Task Force 3/19/1974 - 11/28/1977 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - SLAC (Stanford Linear Accelerator Center) 3/1977 - 5/1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - SRI (Stanford Research Institute): Relations, Plans, etc. 9/1978 - 11/1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - SRI 3/1977 -5/1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University/SRI International Proposed Joint Development Project 3/1981 - 5/1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University: Legal 7/22/1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University: SULA (Stanford University Library Association) 10/1977 - 11/1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - State Disability Insurance 10/1977 - 3/1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University: Affirmative Action 1/1980 - 4/1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Fund Pending Reports 3/1980 - 7/1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University: Other Departments, General 1981 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University: Edward E. Shaw, Associate Provost 8/1979 - 3/1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University: Activity Report of Employees on Lay-off Status 5/1980 - 9/1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University: Stanford University Network 3/30/1980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University: Student Service Meeting 6/24/1976 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Stanford University: Support for Instruction: Undergraduate/Graduate 6/9/1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Stanford University: Student Use: CIT 1981 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Stanford University: Student Records 7/1981 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University: Student Services: Information Systems Support 10/20/1980 - 11/3/1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Stanford University: Stanford Computing Forum 12/1979 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Stanford University: Student Information Network 6/1980 -6/1981 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Stanford University Student Services: CIT 9/1979 - 10/1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Stanford University Student Services: Computing Systems 11/1976 - 2/1981 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Study Group 1982 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - SUNY-Albany Working Party Conference 7/25/1980 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Syntopican 7/1983 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Sytek 7/8/1981 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Surveys and Questionnaires 7/1975 - 7/1979 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Surveys: Datapro 9/1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Taxes 1/1971 - 4/1981 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Task Force 4/1980 - 8/1980 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Task Force Report: Future of Computing at Stanford 1/1981 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Task Force on the Future of Computing at Stanford 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Watsbox 4/1976 - 5/1976 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - TFM: Evaluation Report 9/1981 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - TFM: Evaluation of the TFM Program at Stanford 1981 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - CONTEXT: Text-Handling Network 12/20 proposal 11/1980 - 2/1981 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - CONTEXT: Text-Handling Network 8/1980 - 10/1980 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - CONTEXT 9/1982 - 10/1982 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - CONTEXT: Text Network Program 2/1980 - 12/1982 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - CONTEXT Advisory Council 10/1981 - 5/1982 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Troika Agenda 5/5 8:00 4/1980 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Edward E. Shaw Correspondence to Kennedy, Massy and Crowley 3/1980 - 5/1980 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Technical Information: Computer Conferences 2/1978 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Technical Reports: Computer Economics 11/68 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Technical Reports: Computer Measurement and Evaluation 1/1975 - 11/1975 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Technical Reports: Computer Pricing 5/15/67 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Technical Reports: Documentation Standards 11/13/1974 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Technical Reports: General 5/1975 - 6/1975 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Technical Reports: Hardware 3/1975 - 4/1975 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Technical Reports: IBM 5/1978 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Technical Reports: IBM Multiple Virtual Storage 6/1975 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Technical Reports: Technological Projection 7/1976 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Technical Reports: Network 5/1970 - 8/1976 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Technical Reports: Software Measurement 1/1975 - 8/1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Technical Reports: Teleconferencing 9/1975 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Technical Reports: Academic Computing 11/1973 - 11/1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Technical Reports: ADPS Database Survey 7/1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Technical Reports: BALLOTS 5/1970 - 3/1973 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Technical Reports: CME (Computer Measurement and Evaluation) 11/1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Technical Reports: Controller's Response to Administrative Computing Protocol 12/6/1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Technical Reports: Cross-Assembler/Simulator for a Microprocessor-based IND Control 1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Technical Reports: Database Systems 6/1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Technical Reports: IBM Data Entry Survey 3/1974 - 2/1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Technical Reports: Engineering Services Group 7/1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Technical Reports: GSB (Graduate School of Business) 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Technical Reports: Hardware 4/1974 - 4/1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Technical Reports: Medical Computing 3/1974 - 1/1976 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Technical Reports: Other Universities 5/22/1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Technical Reports: Planning 11/24/1975 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Technical Reports: Program Library Task Force 1/1974 - 1/1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Technical Reports: SCIP 1/1975 - 5/1979 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Telecommunications Services 6/1976 - 1/1977 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Telecommunications 1/1980 - 8/1983 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Technical Data and Reports: Space Management 8/1978 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Technical Reports: SPIRES 9/1971 - 12/1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Technical Reports: Telecommunication Study 9/11/1978 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Technical Data and Reports: Word Processing Project 1/1977 - 7/1978 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Telephone Replacement Project 11/1982 - 7/1983 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Trip Reports 1/1972 - 2/1980 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - University Library Council 12/1981 - 6/1983 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - University Library Council 1981-82 9/1981 - 12/1982 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - University Relations 4/68 - 9/1976 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Users Services Group 6/1970 - 10/1977 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Users Services Group: Document Sales 6/1978 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Utilization: General 12/1974 - 9/1975 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Utilization: Off-site Computing Approvals 9/23/1976 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Utilization: SCIP Income 12/1979 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Utilization: 370/168 Disk 8/1975 - 1/1978 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Utilization: 370/168 General 4/1975 - 3/1979 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Utilization: 370/168 Performance 1/1976 - 5/1978 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Utilization: Campus 3033 10/1980 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - UPS Foundation Meeting 5/1974 - 4/1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - UPS Foundation 2/1980 - 4/1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Navy 8/1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - American Medical Writers Association Western Regional Conference 11/1981 - 5/1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Visitors 7/1981 - 8/1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Wang Users Group 3/1982 - 7/1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - MICOM requests 10/1981 - 12/1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Word Graphics 11/1980 - 5/1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Edward E. Shaw Correspondence & Memoranda 12/1973 – 1/1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Marketing: Academic Computing 5/6/1970 - 4/25/1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Marketing: APL 10/8/1974 - 6/27/1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Marketing: BALLOTS 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Marketing: HIBAL 5/18/1978 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Marketing: LISP 3/9/1979 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Marketing: General 12/3/69 - 9/30/1981 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Marketing: Medical Computing 10/16/1973 - 2/14/1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Marketing: Other Universities 11/19/69 - 6/24/1976 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Marketing: SLAC 3/12/1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Marketing: Software 1/12/1977 - 4/7/1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Marketing: Software 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Marketing: Networks 4/20/1970 - 12/29/1975 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Marketing: On-line Business Systems, General 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Marketing: On-line Business Systems, General 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Marketing: On-line Business Systems, General 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Marketing: On-line Business Systems Wylbur, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Marketing: OBS Software, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Marketing: OBS Business Plan 1982 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Marketing: Orvyl 3/24/1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Marketing: 1974 2/5/68 - 11/19/1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Marketing: Apple 1/12/1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Marketing: Easymark 11/21/1978 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Marketing: SPIRES (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Marketing: SPIRES 11/17/1982 - 5/1/1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Marketing: SPIRES 1/3/1973 - 4/17/1980 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Marketing: SPIRES Consortium 11/23/1982 - 6/17/1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Marketing: SPIRES VM/CMS 10/18/1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Marketing: Stanford 3/10/1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Marketing: Stanford 11/3/66 - 2/1/1979 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Marketing: Tymshare SPIRES, etc. 5/2/1983 - 7/13/1983 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Marketing: US Government 6/1982 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Marketing: WYLBUR 1972-1983 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Marketing: WYLBUR PMI Informatics 8/29/1975 - 1/16/1976 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Marketing: Surveys (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Software 7/7/1983 - 7/8/1983 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - RLG: Software License 1983 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Security (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Selection of Second CPU for Stanford/RLG 3/10/1982 - 3/23/1982 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Services Coordination: CIT 10/7/1982 - 6/20/1983 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Margie Shuer Fellowship Application 12/7/1983 - 2/14/1983 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Electrical Engineering Dept. Siegman Memoranda 9/2/1981 - 5/2/1983 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Space Planning: Jordan Quad 9/22/1981 - 7/11/1983 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Space Planning: Pine Machine Room 9/21/1981 - 2/18/1982 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Space Planning: M & PG Space Project 1/11/1983 - 1/20/1983 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Risk Assessment 11/17/1982 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Stanford University: Miscellaneous 6/12/1981 - 1/11/1983 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Library Computer Literacy 2/15/1983 - 8/17/1983 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - University Searches 8/24/1983 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Vendors: Amdahl 3/18/1982 - 1/13/1983 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Vendors: Fortune System 9/2/1982 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Vendors: Digital 2/1979 - 1/21/1982 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Vendors: Hewlett Packard 4/9/1982 - 2/24/1983 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Vendors: IBM 3081 12/21/1981 - 12/20/1982 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Vendors: 3081 Installation 11/30/1981 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Vendors: 3081B 5/20/1982 - 6/15/1982 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Vendors: Purchase Analysis, IBM 3081 11/13/1982 - 11/17/1982 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Vendors: Intel 8/17/1982 - 11/17/1982 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Vendors: Northern Telecom 3/23/1983 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Vendors: On-line Business Systems 9/3/1981 - 3/21/1983 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Vendors: Storage Technology Corporation 4/16/1982 - 1/19/1983 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Vendors: Miscellaneous 4/26/1982 - 8/2/1983 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Terminals for Managers: Evaluation Report 9/1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - "Future Information Systems at Harvard University" 10/6/1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Hewlett Packard Presentation 11/7/1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Edward E. Shaw: Correspondence & Memoranda 2/1975 – 5/1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Edward E. Shaw: Correspondence & Memoranda 6/1977 - 12/1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Edward E. Shaw: Correspondence & Memoranda 1/1980 – 12/1982 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Edward E. Shaw: Correspondence & Memoranda 8/1981- 1/1983 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Western Electric Sales Packet (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - EARF 912/9/1981 - 6/6/1983 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - CAUSE Recognition Committee 4/1/1983 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - John Chaney Visit 9/9/1982 - 11/3/1982 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - SMIS (Society for Management Information Systems) 8/11/1982 - 9/23/1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Mike M. Roberts: Miscellaneous 1982 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Mike M. Roberts: Correspondence 4/17/1981 - 7/10/1981 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Mike M. Roberts: Routing information 6/21/1982 - 6/30/1982 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Mike M. Roberts: Correspondence & Memoranda 1/1981 - 8/1983 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Mike M. Roberts: Correspondence & Memoranda 5/1978 - 11/1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Mike M. Roberts: Correspondence & Memoranda 12/1978 - 10/1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - EDUNET 10/23/1978 - 1/9/1980 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Budget 5/1/1981 - 12/1/1981 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Forsyth Design and Construction 11/10/1980 - 5/14/1981 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Mike M. Roberts: Archives List (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda 12/15/1981 - 12/29/1981 (Box 31, Folder 17)